S-Sakamoto-han...
Where...
Where are you?
Sakamoto-han...
Sakamoto-han!
Why do you always leave me?
I'm anxious.
Did you abandon me?
Always being left alone...
I'm scared.
I'm hurt, so I'm left out?
Where are you?
You're just ignoring me?
Why won't you tell me anything?!
Why does this have to...
Like with the chips.
...happen to me?
I didn't mean to not tell you.
I was just doing my job.
You didn't tell me...
Life's just a rat race.
...either, did you?
It's kill or be killed.
You have three chips, right?
No one would believe it...
That's all.
I should make these chips...
He's just using me.
...my trump card!
What are they doing here?
I want to go home.
No!
Let me go home.
If I don't, I'll die.
I miss them...
I don't want to die!
I miss them.
I miss them!
Daddy.
Wh-Who's there?
Is someone...
Is someone there?
Are you back, Sakamoto-han?
Daddy.
What?
I heard something.
I've finally gone—
Daddy.
Y-Yuzuhiko!
What are you doing here?!
When did you arrive on this island?
I can't—
I missed you so much...
Why didn't you come home sooner?
I-I couldn't...
I miss you.
I know...
But I'm badly hurt.
And I don't have enough chips yet.
I miss you!
I miss you, too...
Of course I do!
But the chips...
I don't have eight chips.
Sure you do.
Akiko!
Is your mind so far gone
that you can't count?
Count...
How many chips do you have?
How many chips...
One, two...
Three...
That isn't enough, is it?
No, I have more.
Four, five, six...
Seven...
Eight!
I c-can...
I can go home!
Just wait for me, Yuzuhiko... Akiko!
I'm coming! I'm coming home!
And then we can all go eat some good food.
Let's all go to Ajinoya and have
all the okonomiyaki we can eat!
Bonds
It's gotten foggy.
And the sun's starting to set.
The lizards will be waking up soon.
Let's hurry back.
What's wrong?
Shh!
I hear something...
I-It isn't a lizard, is it?
No, this sound...
It can't be...
A homing type?
Ryouta!
It's locked on me.
Ryouta,
run!
This is bad...
If it gets within range, it'll detonate!
A homing type...
The only person with this type of BIM...
It can't be!
Taira-san!
If you're doing this, stop.
We're on the same side!
Ryouta, behind you!
No!
It's within range!
Got him!
Ryouta!
He got my leg...
Th-This is really bad...
Taira-san, please stop!
Why are you doing something so awful?
Why?
Why...
When you get six chips,
the two of you will be tested.
Is Taira-san betraying us
to get all the chips?
No response.
Where is he?
Where's that damned old man hiding?!
Why?
Why did he betray us?
We promised to get out of here together...
So why?
I was scared that maybe
you wouldn't come back,
that you had abandoned me...
It was all I could think about.
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
This time, it's over...
If you leave me here, I...
I won't be able to stay sane.
We need clean towels and water for you.
Don't worry.
We'll come back with some delicious food.
Is it my fault?
No matter what my reasons,
I'm the one who made him feel so anxious.
He was so terrified...
Why didn't I realize?
Was I...
Was I doing
the same thing my dad did?
My dad was obsessed with work,
and never spent any time with me.
And my mom divorced
and remarried without a
damned thought for me.
"Adults are selfish.
They only think about themselves.
They're satisfied with pretending
to care about me."
That was what I thought.
But did I do to Taira-san what I
didn't want done to me,
above all else?
Was I pretending not to see how he felt?
That's right.
You were running away from reality.
Ryouta...
Ryouta!
Snap out of it!
I hear another BIM...
Hurry!
We need to get out of here...
Ryouta!
Run, Himiko!
What are you doing?
Hurry and run!
If the game we're playing has
the same rules as BTOOOM!...
That homing type works just
like it does in the game.
Then I know what I must do.
I know what I...
Himiko!
Wh-What?
I knew it.
It only explodes when it comes
within range of its target.
I'll protect him.
I'll protect Ryouta!
Th-This...
Could it be...
There's no doubt.
Himiko...
She's the same Himiko I met in BTOOOM!.
Taira-san isn't moving.
But he's hiding somewhere we can't see him.
Himiko...
It's okay.
The homing types can only
lock on to a single person.
Leave it to me.
A-All right.
I'm sorry.
Sakamoto-han, Himiko-han...
Don't hate me for this.
You know...
It's a game, right?
Right?
Right,
Yuzuhiko?
Akiko?
It's coming!
Where?
I can hear it...
There.
It doesn't matter how many you send!
Doesn't something seem off here?
If he really intended to kill me,
would he waste his BIMs like this?
No, he wouldn't.
He's smarter than that.
That means that BIM is headed for...
Taira-san's target is
you, Himiko!
I did it.
I outsmarted him!
H-He outsmarted me.
D-Damn...
Damn!
Taira-san...
C-Crap...
Taira-san! Taira-san!
No...
He's going to kill me.
Stay away!
Taira-san!
Stop this, and come back!
Ryouta...
Ryouta!
M-My hip...
Taira-san!
They're going to kill me...
I only have one left?
I have to kill him before he kills me.
For Yuzuhiko!
For Akiko!
Taira-san,
where are you?
Taira-san, I want to apologize to you.
I want to...
I want to go back with you!
I want to go home with you.
I won't worry you again.
I'll do it right this time...
Please just give me one more chance!
Please, Taira-san...
Please let me apologize, Taira-san.
Taira-san!
S-Sakamoto-han, I...
I... I...
This is karma, isn't it?
Punishment for what I did.
Sorry, Sakamoto-han, Himiko-han.
I just wanted to go home...
I missed my family.
That was all.
Yuzuhiko... Akiko...
I'm sorry...
Daddy can't take any more pain.
Taira-san?
Why?
Why did this happen?
Weren't we going to return together?
Stand up...
Say something!
Tell me another stupid joke
like you always do!
Start eating your instant
ramen before it's cooked!
I never got to apologize to you...
Why?
Why?!
Do you think Taira-san planned
to betray us the whole time?
Like Date-san?
No, he wasn't like that.
He was just a normal person.
And that's why he got scared and suspicious.
No one wants to die.
And everyone wants to go home.
So when he got hurt,
and was alone with despair closing in...
His heart broke.
I...
I basically killed him!
Do you want to go home, too?
Yeah, I want out of here...
Away from this hell.
You can leave, Ryouta.
I can?
Yes.
I took these chips from back there.
One of them is Taira-san's.
And he took the other two without telling us.
With these and the three
we found, it makes six.
Plus one from me,
and one from you.
Those are the eight you need
to leave the island.
If one of us dies, one can leave.
So kill me.
Yes.
This is right.
I don't have anywhere to return to.
When I had nowhere to go, you changed me.
I feel like even if we weren't connected
in the real world, our hearts were.
Even if the world was virtual,
you saved me.
Then, when I came to this island
and almost died so many times...
Even when I almost fell apart.
So now, I understand...
You are my hope for survival.
Ryouta...
If you survive,
if you live...
I don't care what happens to me.
I don't care.
D-Don't be stupid!
You think I want to go home
so much that I'd sacrifice you?
Do you think that's the kind of guy I am?
I won't abandon you!
I wouldn't ever...
Not in this world or the virtual one!
You're the Himiko from the game, aren't you?
I finally realized...
I finally got to see you.
Himiko...
I always...
I always wanted to meet you.
Himiko?
That's right.
She's still scared...
She should be scared.
But for me, she's doing her best not to be.
But I...
Not going to do it?
Remember what I told you?
The first one to move wins.
Show her what a man you are...
Or are you still satisfied with
holding yourself back?
Sh-Shut up!
You'll never catch up to me that way.
Shut up!
I don't
look up to you anymore!
I finally understand...
What matters is to care for others.
If I'd known that,
I wouldn't have let Taira-san die.
I could've gotten along with my family.
I thought I was the only one that mattered...
I looked down on others.
If I hadn't, I never would've
been brought to this island!
Oda...
I'm not like you.
I won't be like you...
Get out of my heart!
Ryouta?
Is something wrong?
Sorry for being so sudden.
But doing this here,
in the heat of a moment...
It's not right.
Himiko, let's leave this island together.
Let's go back together!
And then...
I'll start dating you officially.
Yes.
This is right.
I'm going to leave this hell with Himiko.
Twenty-four hours...
Get it back on-line in
twenty-four hours!
Once you get to the island,
begin at once.
Got it?
Understood.
Goodbye.
Make sure the clients don't
find out about this.
Y-Yes, sir.
Mechanical trouble on the
island now, of all times...
Of all the times!
Ryouta, I'm sorry.
This is all that I can do.